Guide to the Records of the Office of Library Administration RG.38.0.1
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of Library Administration
1946-1995
RG.38.0.1
New York University Archives
15.0 linear feet
The Office of Library Administration oversees the development of library programming, collections, events, staff and general administration of libraries at New York University. This collection contains the records of the New York University Library Offices from the period 1960-1996. These include memos, reports, brochures, minutes and planning documents.
New York University. Office of Library Administration.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files with information that falls under the University's Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) policy are permanently restricted.
Please contact the University Archivists with specific questions regarding restrictions.
Scope and Contents Note
This collection contains the records of the New York University Library Offices from the period 1960-1996. The records are comprised of mixed materials pertinent to library operations, collections, staffing, events, development, planning, public affairs, administration, supplies, and construction. These include memos, reports, brochures, minutes and planning documents.
Arrangement
The files are grouped into three series:
Series I: Alphabetical Subject Files
Series II: Development and Events
Series III: Budget and Planning
Folders are arranged alphabetically.
Historical Note
The Office of Library Administration oversees the development of library programming, collections, events, staff and general administration of libraries at New York University.
Brademas, John, 1927-; Elmer Holmes Bobst Library.; McNaughton Hester, James; New York University. Faculty of Arts and Science.; New York University.; Oliva, Lawrence Jay, 1933-; Sawhill, John C., 1936-; Construction and architecture.; Elmer Holmes Bobst Library.; Libraries |z New York (State); Libraries.; New York University |x Budget.; New York University |x Development.; New York University |x Fundraising.; New York University |x Special events.; New York University. University Senate.
- Series I: Alphabetical Subject Files, 1946-1995; 10.0
  - Academic Affairs, 1979-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Computing Committee, Future of, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Convocation, September 12th, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academic Planning and Services, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Acquisition Fund, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Acquisition Policy, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Acquisitions: Special Items, 1964-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Acrophobia Study, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Space Utilization, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Council, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Management Council 1, 1970-1972, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Management Council 2, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Policies and Procedures, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Adminstrative Services, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Admissions: Comparative Data, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Advertising and Publications, Office of, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Affirmative Action, 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Afro-American Institute, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Agnew, Dr. Peter, 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ALA Gala Open House, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Alumnae Club, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Association Club, 1957-1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Federation: Calendar of Events, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Fund, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Relations Office, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - American Library Association, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - American Library Association: Library Administration Division, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - American Records Management Association, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - American Society of Indexers, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - American Society for Public Administration, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Annual Reports: Dean of Libraries, 1961-1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Annunciator Board, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Anthropology Collection (Wenner-Gren), 1977-1979, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Applicants for Dean of Library, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Appointments, 1965-1973 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Archives, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Archons of Colophon, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Arts and Science Faculty, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Agenda, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Candidates for Deanship of Washington Square University College, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Committee on Committees, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Correspondence, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Departmental Priorities and Collection Development, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Library Committee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Student Library Committee, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Arts and Science Faculty: Undergraduate Division Proposed New Courses, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Arts and Science Graduate Commission: Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Arts and Science Graduate Commission: Reports and Proposals, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Arts and Science Graduate Student Council, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Athletics, Department of, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Atrium Research, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Audio Visual Services, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Automation House, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Balance of Trade Study, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Avery Fischer Music and Listening Center, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Basic Document for Librarians, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Basic List of "Frozen" in Bobst Library, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Benchmark Committee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Bicentennial, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Board of Standards and Appeal, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Board of Trustees, 1976-1986 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Bobst Library, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Bobst Architects Meeting I, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Bobst Architects Meeting II, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bobst Architects Meeting III, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bobst Coler Lounge, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bobst Convocations, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bobst Convocation and Dedication Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bobst Floor Plans, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bobst Move, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bobst Naming Gifts, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bobst Planning Schedules, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bobst Problems, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bobst Procedures, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Book Inventory, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Booklet for Bobst, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Brynildsen, Palmer, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Budget: General, 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Budget: Information, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Budget: Construction Estimates, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Budget: Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Budget: Office of the Director, 1954-1959 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Budget: Planning, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Budget: Planning, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Building Planning and Research, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Business Administration, Graduate School of, 1973-1987 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Business and Public Administration, School of, 1963-1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bylaws, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - C.S. Brown and Company, 1963-1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Capacity Reports, 1966-1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Capital Budgeting, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Capital Program, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Capital Program, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Capital Program, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Capital Program, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Capital Program, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Capital Program, 1964-1969 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Card Cabinets, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Card Catalog, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Card Distribution, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Carpeting, 1965-1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Carrels, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Catalog Card Duplication, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Catalog Card Production, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Catalog Cards, 1962-1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cataloging: Comparative Statistics, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chancellor's Award for Administrators, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Chancellor's Award for Students, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chancellor's Office: Provost, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Chancellors Office: Vice Provost, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Charging System, 1949, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Check Requests, 1964-1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chemical Fund Endowment, 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Circulation, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Classics Department, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Classics Department, 1973-1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Classics Department: Coins, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Coat Room, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Coles Recreation Center, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Collection Development, 1964-1981 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Commencement, 1972-1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Commerce School, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Current Teaching Loads, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Community Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Community Relations, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Complaints, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Computer Applications, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Computing Center, 1978-1984 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Conference Room, 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Conflict of Interest Disclosures, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Conservation Center, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Construction Progress, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Consultants, 1965-1972 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Continuing Education School, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Continuing Education School: Book Publishing, 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Conveyor, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Copy Center, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Copyright and Dissertation Policies, 1961-1975 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1987 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Data Processing and Machine Operations, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Data Processing Planning, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Day in Albany, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Dean's Council, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dean's Meeting, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Deans of the Night Committee, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Dean's Task Force on the Graduate School, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Dental Library, 1963-1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dentistry, School of, 1970-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Dentistry, School of: Dental Center Newsletter, 1976-1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Department and Unit Head Meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Description of Libraries, 1949-1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Deutsches Haus, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Development Campaign, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Development: Fund Raising Activities, 1972-1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Development: Leadership Campaign, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Development, miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Development Office, 1966-1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Development, University, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Directive: Bobst Public Service Operative, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Director of Libraries: Real Estate, 1967-1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Directory, 1964-1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Dock Reference, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Donor Awareness Plan, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Eberstadt Library, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Education, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Education Training Committee, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Elevators, 1966-1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Employees, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Engineering, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - English, Department, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Exchange Agreement with University of Paris, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Executive Policy Committee, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - External Affairs, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Facilities, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Faculty, Library, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Faculty Club, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Faculty Council, 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Faculty Council Newsletter, 1977-1986 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Faculty Development Committee, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Faculty Legal Protection, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Faculty Meeting Agenda and Memoranda, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Faculty Policy, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Resources Network Program, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Faculty Resources Network Program, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Faculty Staff Policies and Procedures, 1979-1986 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Faculty Women's Club, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Fales, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Family Education Rights and Privacy Act, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Feinberg, Charles, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Film Library, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Finance, 1962-1985 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Finance Office, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Financial Exigency Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Fire Marshalls, undated, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - First Editions Club, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - First Editions Club, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Fiscal Review Group, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Five-Year Plan, 1980-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Five-Year Projects, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Foreign LYL, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fried, Henry, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Funds, Special Library, 1965-1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Furniture and Equipment Estimates, 1965-1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin Associates, 1957-1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Gallatin Bulletin, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Gallatin Division, 1981-1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - General Counsel, 1968-1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - German House Fund, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Gifts, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gold, Meyer, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Governance Report, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Grant Applications, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Grey Gallery, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Grieder, 1968-1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Hart, Joseph T., 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Heights, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Higher Education Opportunity Program, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - History, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - History Department Correspondence, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Holdings of NYU Libraries, 1963-1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Holocaust Center, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Honorary Curators, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Housing, 1965-1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Housing, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Humanities Council, 1976-1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - IBM Equipment, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - ID Cards, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - ID Cards, NYU, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Illuminating Engineers, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - IMC, 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Independent Student Coalition, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Information Center, 1977-1986 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Institute for Economic Analysis: I.E.A Library, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Insurance, 1965-1972 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - International Student Center, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - International Theater Institute, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Interschool Colloquia and Study Groups, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Inventory, 1962-1967 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Inventory, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Jazz, 1984-1994 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Joint Faculty-Library Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Joint Faculty- Librarians Committee Meeting Minutes and Agenda, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Journalism, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Journalism, Department of, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Judiac and Hebrew Studies, Institute of, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Key- Punch, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Keys and Door Schedule, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kirschenbaumm David, 1966-1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Kirschenbaum, David- Rare Book Fund, 1958-1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Kurth, William- Consultant, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - LAD Buildings Institute San Francisco June 1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - LAD Advisory Committee, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Law School- Telecommunication and Information Revolution, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Legal Counsel, 1981-1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Levy Johnson BN Purchase, 1978-1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Library Association, 1966-1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Library/Bookstore Task-Force, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Library/Bookstore Task Force, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Library Campaign, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Library Committee- General Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Library Construction, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Library Cooperation, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Library Council, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Library Journal, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Library Organization, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Lighting, 1961-1968 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Livingston Papers, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Machlup Survey, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Master Plan Report, 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Master Plan 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Media, 1973-1978 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Medical Center, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Meeting Minutes (Library Planning), 1964 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Meluil Dui, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Mercantile Library Association, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Mezzanine, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm NMA, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Middle States Association Accreditation, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Committees, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Motion Picture, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Moving, 1966-1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Multimedia Center, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Music Department, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Music Library, 1968-1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Musical Theatre, 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Musical Theatre Archives, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - NASA Acts Program, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - National Research University I, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NMA Finance, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - NMA Standards, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - NSPA, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Near Eastern Studies, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Network, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - New Book Areas, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - New Building Washington Square, 1963-1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - New York City Partnership Surveys, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - NYLA, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - New York Metropolitan Reference and Research Library Agency (folder 1 of 3), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - New York Metropolitan Reference and Research Library Agency (folder 2 of 3), 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - New York Metropolitan Reference and Research Library Agency (folder 3 of 3), 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - New York University Club, 1974-1985 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - NYU in Italy, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - NYULAN, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - NYU Libraries, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - NYU in the News, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - NYU Magazine, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - NYU Medical Center: Capital Fund (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - NYU Notebook, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - NYU Press Releases, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - NYU Report, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Occupancy Schedules, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Office of Vice President for Administration, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Onassis Center, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - One Hundred Million Fund Drive, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - One Million Dollars A Week, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - On-Line Catalog, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - On-line Catalogue Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Operations, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Organization Plan- G.U.L., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Patents- Invitatons, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Personnel Estimates, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Personnel Issues, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Photocopy Vending Machines, 1967-1971 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Pneumatic Tubes, 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - President's Council of Libraries, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Program- 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Prospects, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Psychology, Department of, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Public Administration, 1969-1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Public Affairs General Publicity, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Public Affairs Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Public Service Mtg., 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Publications and Printing, 1961-1965 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Public Relations, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Reader's Services Monthly Reports, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Office of Real Estate, 1979-1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Reference and Building Services, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Reference Department Monthly Reports, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Reference Division and Reader's Services Minutes, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Reports, Library, 1965-1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Reports from the President, 1962-1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Report of Technical Services Catalog Committee, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Research Libraries, 1963-1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Reserve, 1964-1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Rosenthal Fellowship, 1952-1971 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Russian, 1966-1972 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Salary, Background Data and Fringe Benefits, 1964-1972 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Scholastic, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Science, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Security- Loss of Books, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Security System, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Scientific Research Committee Policy, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - SEHNAP, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - SEHNAP, Dean Search Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - SEHNAP, Film Library Fall 1983 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - SEHNAP, Health/Nursing, 1965-1983 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - SEHNAP, Proposal for Doctor of Arts Degree, 1975-1985 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Senate, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Senate Library Committees, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Senate, University- Advisory Committee on Libraries, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Senate, University- Committee on Organizatio Governance (SCOG), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Senate, University- Committee on Organization and Governance, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Senate, University- General Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Senate Judicial Board, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Senate Judicial Board- Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Senate Meetings, University, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Senate Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Senate, University- Public Affairs Committee (Gay People's Union), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Senate Records, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Sesquicentennial Gift to local libraries, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Shelving, 1961-1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Social Science, 1964-1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)